http://camosun.ca/privacy-statement.html

Information • November 26, 2020 8:01 am • New restrictions to combat rising number of cases of COVID-19 • Read more…
Continuing Education Courses A-Z
Dual Credit (SIP)
Cafeterias
Camosun College Student Society (CCSS)
Dual Credit (SIP) Forms
Room Bookings (Students/CCSS)
About Indigenous Education
Are You of Indigenous Ancestry?
Website privacy statement
Camosun College respects the privacy of personal information and strives to maintain the public’s trust through transparency and accountability in its use of personal information. Personal information is information which can be used to distinguish, identify, or contact an individual specifically and which is not publicly available. This website exists to benefit the Camosun community, its supporters, and the public. Use is free and anonymous except where sign-in is required. If you choose to send us personal information you consent to its collection and use by the College. The personal information you provide may be used by the College to correspond with you, for registration, to process a donation, for surveys, and for other purposes that are consistent with the purpose for which the information was provided. The College may share this information with the College Foundation and its Alumni Association. The College will not disclose personal information you provide to any other third party without your permission unless required to do so by law. All personal information is protected in accordance with the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act.
To provide effective website search results, camosun.ca sends information anonymously to google.com. This information is used only for statistical purposes with no personally identifiable information sent.
Our password protocols and encryption software are routinely updated to maximize protection of personal and other information. While we strive to protect personal information, please note that no Internet data transmission is completely secure. This policy is regularly reviewed and updated to reflect our practices. See all Camosun College policies
Last updated: April 4, 2017 10:04 am
Contact Us
Camosun College Lansdowne
3100 Foul Bay Rd
Victoria BC V8P 5J2
Camosun College Interurban
4461 Interurban Rd
Victoria BC V9E 2C1
1–877–554–7555 (toll-free)
©1996–2020 Camosun College • Victoria BC, Canada • Privacy statement • Website Feedback
©1996–2020 Camosun College | Victoria BC, Canada | Printed: December 10, 2020 at 11:09 pm
